(Stuart:)I'm sorry,
you mumbled something?
(Raj:)It's just that
(Raj:)they've had plenty of help.
(Stuart:)Well, you know what they say--
it takes a village.
(Raj:)Well, they already
had a village.
(Stuart:)I noticed the village
couldn't find time
(Stuart:)to put the crib together.
(Raj:)Yeah, well, maybe
(Raj:)the village was too busy
checking out
(Raj:)the local Montessori school
for the new arrival.
(Stuart:)You mean the one
(Stuart:)with the empty beer bottles
in the sandbox?
(Stuart:)We'll pass, thank you.
(Bernadette:)Do something, Batman.
(Leonard:)Hey.
(Sheldon:)What do you think you're doing?
(Leonard:)Separating my delicates.
(Sheldon:)This is the level
you're stooping to.
(Sheldon:)No.
(Sheldon:)This is the level
I am stooping to.
(Leonard:)I believe that is flag
to crotch four, checkmate.